Mss.Ms.Coll.115
American Philosophical Society
- Series V. Francis Fisher Kane, 1880-1955; Francis Fisher Kane (1866-1955) was a Philadelphia lawyer and U.S. Attorney for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, 1913-1920. This collection of letters, reports, briefs, and documents, reflects Kane's politically liberal interests in Indian rights, pri
  - Papers, 1856-1952; 4.0 lin. feet
    - Committee of 100, 1950
      Form letter and reprints from the St. Petersburg Times.
    - Committee on the Southern Utes, 1891
      Notes of a speech.
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania vs. Antico et al, 1941
      Regarding Minority Parties.
    - Concerning the Ute Indians #1, 1891
      Notes.
    - Concerning the Ute Indians #2, 1892 February 3
      Th. Morgan, Indian Affairs.
    - Concerning the Ute Indians #3, 1892-1893
      Booth, Ogden, Peel, Temperance Union.
    - Conference on Peaceful alternatives to the Atlantic Pact, 1949
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane #1, 1880-1884
      His sister; nicknamed "Lila".
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane #2, 1917-1922
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane #3, 1931-1951
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane #4, Undated
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane to Mrs. R.P. Kane, 1916-1919
      From his sister to their mother.
    - Cope, Eliza Middleton Kane-Letters in memory, 1952-1953
      Condolences on death of his sister.
    - Cope, Elizabeth, Undated
      His neice.
    - Cope, Francis R., 1904, 1909
      1904 September 10-Political letter; the "Negro question"; 1909 January 21-Contributions to earthquake fund.
    - Cope, Henry, 1915
    - Cope, Oliver, 1920
      Two postcards to his nephew; one thank-you letter from nephew for gift of a watch.
    - Cope, Thomas P., 1914-1922
      To and from his nephew; some concern a legal case involving the IWW.
    - Corry, James C., 1916-1922
    - Court of Common Pleas, Philadelphia, 1904 June 1
      Requests death certificate of William J. Canning.
    - Coxe, Anna B., Undated
      Invitation; regarding Ellis H.R. Brooks.
    - Coxe, Eckley B., 1917-1922
    - Coxe, Maria M., 1885
      A cousin?
    - Coxe, Sophia Fisher, 1913-1937, n.d.
      Letters from Aunt to F.F.K. & Mother.
    - Creasey, William T., 1906, 1907
      Regarding Democratic Party politics.
    - Crown, Philip, 1919
    - Curry, Margaret A., 1922 January 20
      Regarding investments.
    - D, 1914-1922
    - Dallett, Morris, 1910 April 13
      Regarding a horse.
    - Dana, Millicent, Undated
      Regarding commencement exercises.
    - Daniel, Todd, 1920-1922, 1949
      Law partner of Henry Walnut.
    - Daniels, Joseph M., 1918, 1920
    - Darling, M.H., 1921
    - Darrach, Grace, 1949 August 25
      Soliciting him for typing jobs.
    - Daughtey, Harry M., 1921
      U.S. Attorney General; regarding IWW case and E. Debs.
    - Davis, John W., 1922
      Request invitation for Miss Florence Wyer of Scotland to White House reception.
    - Delk, Edwin Heyl, 1922
    - Democratic National Committee, 1919
    - Democratic State Committee, 1915, 1919
    - Derby, Richard C., 1918-1922
    - DeSchweinitz, G.E., 1919, 1922
    - Deutsch, Albert, 1949 August 4
      To Negley Teeters, Temple Criminology professor regarding pre-trial detention in county jails.
    - Devries, Mary C., 1885 December 11
    - Devries, William Levering #1, 1882-1883
      Friend from St. Paul's School.
    - Devries, William Levering #2, 1884
      Describes performances by E. Booth.
    - Devries, William Levering #3, 1885
    - Devries, William Levering #4, 1919, 1921
    - Dick, J. Nelson, 1919
    - Dickson, Arthur G., 1915-1922
    - Dickson, Janet, 1921
      Social engagement; Italian addresses.
    - Dickson, Samuel, 1905
      Hellenic Society, excursions to Greece.
    - Diplomatic and Consular officers of the United States of America, 1926, 1931
    - Dougherty, D. Cardinal (Archbishop of Philadelphia), 1948
      Both object to universal military training.
    - Dow, Margaret Elder #1, 1927-1932
      Regarding Biography of E.K. Kane (F.F.K.'s uncle); includes refusal to endorse the book.
    - Dow, Margaret Elder #2, 1937-1938
    - Draper, Martha L., 1917-1918
    - Duane, Russell, 1915-1917, 1936
      Concerning obituary of cousin John Cadwalader, Jr. for the American Philosophical Society.
    - DuPont, E. Paul, 1917, 1933
      City directory information on John K. Kane.
    - DuPont, George, 1949
      Copies of Christmas card with child's photo.
    - DuPont, Jean Kane Foulke, 1950, 1952
      Daughter of his cousin; personal correspondence, wants to buy him a suit for Temple honorary degree ceremony.
    - Durand, E., 1859, 1920
      Regarding author's pamphlet "The Botany of the Great Salt Lakes of Utah."
    - Durrell, Anthony W., 1920-1921
      Asks for special permission to meet his aunt and uncle at the wharf.
    - E, 1915-1924
    - Eastern State Penitentiary, 1947-1948
      Also called New Eastern State Penitentiary, Graterford, Pa.
    - Ebert, S. Anna, 1949 October 24
      Thanks him for stamps sent to hospital.
    - Edmonds, Franklin S., 1905 December 13
      Excuses himself from a committee meeting.
    - Eisenbrown, William, 1909 March 1
      Sends regrets regarding invitation to attend the Junior Legal Club meeting.
    - Elder, Margaret, 1924-1926
    - Elliot, Mrs., 1921-1922
      Notes and drafts for typing to his secretary.
    - Elliot, S., 1921 July 15
      Letter regarding Mrs. Kane's will.
    - Ellis, Mary R., 1883
      Thank you note; friendly letter.
    - Emerson, W.K.B., 1918-1920
    - Emery, Lewis, Jr., 1906 July 3
      Lincoln Republicans; mentions Mr. Coray.
    - Evans, Edward W., 1921
      Trying to arrange a meeting.
    - Everitt, Frank B., 1949
      Regarding illness, mutual friends.
    - F, 1915-1922
    - Farabee, William Curtis, 1921
      Congratulatory letter; dinner invitation.
    - Farnum, Paul, 1885 November 24
      His cousin; discusses Princeton/Yale game.
    - Fels, Samuel, 1921 August 2
      Letter of introduction for A.J. Muste.
    - Fern Rock, Undated
      Judge Kane's house; distances from steps.
    - Fidelity Trust Company, 1917, 1923-1924
    - Fire Association of Philadelphia, 1919
    - Fisher, Eliza Middleton, Undated
      Birthday greetings from his grandmother.
    - Fisher, George Harrison, 1915-1925
    - Fisher, Henry M., 1910
      His uncle; vacation letter and invitation.
    - Fisher, Henry M.- regarding death of, 1939
      Includes memoir of Joseph Walsh.
    - Fisher, H.W. and Company, 1915-1922
    - Fisher, J. Francis, 1932
      Grandfather's card; note from F.F.K.
    - Fisher, James M., 1892 February 29
      Requests copy of speech for Indian Committee.
    - Flanders, Henry, 1903-1909
      Congratulates F.F.K. on nomination for Democratic candidate for mayor; politics.
    - Fletcher, Angus, 1920
    - Fletcher, Ethel, Undated
      Coming from England to the United States.
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1922 January 26
      Regarding luncheon speaking engagement for F.F.K.
    - Fort Lewis, Colorado, 1891
      1890-1891 snowfall. Receipt from Capt. Macauley to Mr. Ritter.
    - Fortner, James, 1921
    - Foulke, Jean Kane, 1949
      His cousin; family concerns.
    - Fow, John H., 1906 April 6
      Notary public.
    - Fox, Charles Edwin, 1921 December 7
      Regarding reform of criminal procedures.
    - Fox, William Logan, 1918-1919
    - Foy, Furman T., 1914
      Legal matters regarding transfer of watch repair business.
    - Fraley, Fred, Undated
      F.F.K.'s friend not voted into [Shakespeare] Society.
    - Francis, Percy, 1918
    - Fraternal Co-op League of Philadelphia, 1921 October 20
      F.F.K. spoke to them on the Russian famine.
    - Frazier, B.W., 1922 February 27
      Dinner invitation to discuss the future of the Men's Club of Church of Our Savior.
    - Fredericks, Paul, 1921 August 25
      Regarding care of F.F.K.'s mother's grave.
    - Freeman and Company, Auctioneers, 1921
      Two receipts for items received.
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1952 April 7
      Regarding immigration laws.
    - Friends Hospital, 1915-1922
    - Friendship Liberal League, 1921
      Invitation to speak at the League.
    - G, 1914-1924
    - Gest, John Marshall, 1918
    - Geter, John, 1922
    - Gibboney, D. Clarence, 1921
      Business; Junior Legal Club.
    - Gibbons, Henry J., 1914-1919, 1943
    - Gibbons, Michael J., 1924
    - Gibbs, Edward, 1948
      Prisoner in New Eastern State Penitentiary.
    - Gilbert, D., 1914-1915
    - Gilpin, William Bernard, 1880-1885
      School friend, working in insurance.
    - Girard Trust Company, 1915-1923
    - Giretti, Eduardo, 1915
      Regarding Italian-American trade.
    - Glasgow, William A., Jr., 1915
    - Glazer, Benjamin, 1950
      Regarding correspondence concerning Mr. Fraser and the Survey award.
    - Goepp, Philip H., 1871
      Regarding visit and death of a friend.
    - Goldman, Bernard, 1921
      Regarding loan to Goldman, who is studying languages and engineering.
    - Goodis, David, 1922 March 19
      Requesting information on costs of court maintenance in Pennsylvania; Wharton student.
    - Goodwin, George S., 1921 December 9
      Accuses F.F.K. of not being "for the people".
    - Goodwin, James, 1882 November 19
      Discusses "Scientific Association" and relative merits of Trinity vs. Princeton.
    - Gordon, G.B., 1918-1920
    - Gray, William A., 1920-1922
    - Green, J.W.P., 1914
      Sends package of F.F.K.'s father's papers.
    - Greenfield, Arthur D., 1919-1921
      Regarding drugs, addiction, and the law.
    - Gregory, T., 1915-1916
      Regarding Supreme Court nomination.
    - Groton, John M., 1920-1923
      Loan for education, sermon on death of Mr. Meigs; F.F.K. to teach eight lessons on the parables.
    - Guthrie, George W., 1906 February 21
      Regarding election congratulations.
    - H, 1906-1950
    - Haas, Otto, 1922
    - Hahn, Eugene, 1924
    - Hanby, Annie B., 1884 June 5
      Note from elderly lady.
    - Harlan, Earle, 1951 January 20
      Memories of earlier days, law office of Hunter & Fisher.
    - Harris, William, Undated
      Two invitations, one with notes on Greek literature.
    - Hart, W.O., 1918, 1922
      Inquiry about final resting palce of E.K.K.
    - Hart, Mrs. William H., 1925-1938
      Regarding the Herring family diary.
    - Hartman, W.A., 1914
    - Hassrick, Romain C., 1917-1920
    - Hatch, Charles B., 1920
    - Hay, Edward N., 1940
      Regarding Cincinnati Gazatte clipping of March 7, 1857 concerning E.K.K.
    - Hazlett, James V., 1923
    - Hearing aids, 1950-1951
      Regarding purchase, repair and use of.
    - Heberton, G. Van Gelder, 1934 November 16
      Regarding historical document involving John K. Kane.
    - Heckscher, Stevens, 1922
    - Heine, H. Eugene, 1922
    - Hensel, W.U., 1905-1911
      Politics, grandfather Judge Kane.
    - Hewitt, Luther E., 1917
    - Hibben, Paxton, 1922
      Politics, famine in Russia, speaking engagement in Philadelphia.
    - Hibberd, D.P., 1921 November 3
      Thanks for finding Mallet a position.
    - Hicks, William Cleveland, Jr., 1882-1885
      School friend.
    - Hill, Virginia J., 1922
    - Hitchins, Charles, 1921-1922
      Thanks for kindness, gift or loan of money.
    - Hoffman, Paul G., 1949 May 18
      Address before group of civic and business leaders of Lehigh Valley on communism.
    - Hoopes, Herman, 1917
    - Horn, Joseph V., 1949 December 15
      Gift from estate to Voluntary Defenders' Committee.
    - Hoskins, W. Horace, 1914-1915
    - Houghton, Alanson Bigelow, 1922
    - Howe, Walter B., 1949 October 3
      Princeton Alumni fundraising letter.
    - Hughes, William J., 1921 October 18
      Thanks for helping F.F.K. to return to Federal Service.
    - I, 1891-1921
    - Indian Rights Association #1, 1891
      Regarding Ute removal; F.F.K. on Association board.
    - Indian Rights Association #2, 1892
      Reports, appeal letters, correspondence.
    - Indian Rights Association #3, 1894
    - Indian Rights Association #4, 1934, 1950-1951
    - Indianapolis Water Works Securities Company, 1919
    - Ingersoll, C.E., 1907 March 8
      Declines social invitation.
    - Insurance Company of North America, 1917, 1923
    - Intercollegiate Liberal League, 1921
      Possible speaking engagements on disarmament.
    - Intercollegiate Socialist Society, 1921
      Sympathetic, but declines speaking opportunity because not socialist.
    - International Association of Machinists, 1922
      Regarding man posing as an attorney.
    - International Free Trade League, 1921 October 24
      Fundraising letter to get newspaper out.
    - International Mercantile Marine Lines, 1920
    - Invitations
      Printed and by hand.
    - Irey, Elmer, 1921
    - J, 1915-1922
    - Jacobs, William M., 1923
    - Jaffe, Lena I., Undated
      To F.F.K.'s sister, regarding F.F.K. winning the Bok award and his humanitarianism.
    - Jamieson, W.D., 1917-1920
    - January, Josephine P., Undated
      "Dear Uncle Frank"
    - Jayne, H. LaBarre, 1915
    - Jefferys, Edward M., 1919-1920
    - Jenkins, Theodore F., 1906, 1908
      Lawyer, regarding politics and law school.
    - John, Joseph G., 1908
      Business?
    - Johnson, Ellis C., 1919-1920
    - Johnson, Euphemia, Undated
      New Year's greeting.
    - Jones, J. Levering, 1896, 1915-1920
      Typescript of letter of recommendation for F.F.K. as assistant District Attorney.
    - Jordon, Ella D., 1883?
      Social invitation; her engagement.
    - Journal of American History, 1922 February 4
      Regarding E.K.K. illustrations in 1920 issue.
    - Junior Legal Club, 1915-1917
    - K, 1906-1926
    - Kane, Anne Francis, 1883-1885
    - Kane, Bayard #1, 1919-1924
      Regarding J.K.K. biography.
    - Kane, Bayard #2, 1931 March 20
      Regarding J.K.K.'s portrait in Judge Dickinson's courtroom; mentions John F. Lewis.
    - Kane, E.D., 1890-1904
      From Robert P. Kane's sister-in-law, regarding Bringham Young, Mormons.
    - Kane, Elisha Kent, 1856 September 1
      To Robert Patterson Kane.
    - Kane, Elisha Kent, 1910 March 20
      Son of Thomas Leiper Kane, cousin, regarding business.
    - Kane, Elisha Kent, 1918-1924
      To cousin, regarding fire.
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #1, 1880-1885
      Mother.
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #2, 1886
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #3, 1887-1890
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #4, 1891-1892
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #5, 1893-1895
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #6, 1900-1905
    - Kane, Elizabeth Francis Fisher #7, 1915-1919
    - Kane, Florence Bayard, 1915-1922
      His cousin; Asks for advice on European lodgings.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher, 1915-1940, undated
      Addresses in South America.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Associations, Undated
      List of F.F.K's membership.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Beck, Robinson & Kane, 1910 October 1
      Card announcing F.F.K. joining law firm.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Certificates, 1880-1946
      From various organizations.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-College of New Jersey, 1885 December 28
      Senior year report card.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-"Cruise of the Triumvirate", Undated
      Log of youthful canoeing adventure.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Daybook, 1949
      Calendar of appointments, etc.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Diary, Europe, 1905
      Trip with Jack Cadwalader.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Diary, Vienna, 1920
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Election material, Undated
      Advertisement to vote for F.F.K. for representative.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-"Element of Moral Character in Presidential Candidates", 1884 October
      College essay, junior year.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Estate #1, 1948-1949
      Budgeting expenses with help of nephew, Dr. Oliver Cope.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Estate #2, 1940-1950
      Budgeting, income listings.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-"Free Institutions and Municipal Government", 1886 June 11
      Speech.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-"The Moral of Ulysses", 1885 January 28
      College essay, Junior year.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Notebook of trip, 1891
      To Durango, Colorado by F.F.K and others.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Notebook on law, Undated
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Notes, law and biographical, Undated
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Obituary, 1955 May 28
      From the Providence (Rhode Island) Journal.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-"Of Abandonment", Undated
      Translation of legal work.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Photographs, Undated
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Poetry, Undated
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Postcards, 1901, 1904
      To parents; from trips to Europe, St. Louis World's Fair.
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Printing advertisement, 1877 May 14
    - Kane, Francis Fisher-Wills, 1948, 1950
    - Kane, Harry Francis, 1950 December 9
      Regarding liberal politics and old age.
    - Kane, Jean Duval Leiper, 1885
      Regarding social engagements.
    - Kane, John Kent, 1917-1919
    - Kane, John Kintzing, 1883-1888
      Two short biographies, plus handwritten notes.
    - Kane, John Kintzing, 1949-1950
      Regarding publishing and distributing Grandfather's autobiography.
    - Kane, John Kintzing-Notebook, 1815
      Poetry, financial records, etc. Includes name of T.M. Hopkinson.
    - Kane, Peggy H., 1944 January 11
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1901, undated
      Father. From F.F. Kane.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1880
      To F.F. Kane.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1880
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #3, 1880
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1881
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1881
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #3, 1881
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #3, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #4, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #5, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #6, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #7, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #8, 1882
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #3, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #4, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #5, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #6, 1883
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1884
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1884
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #1, 1885
    - Kane, Robert Patterson #2, 1885
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, 1906 June 23
      From unidentified person.
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
    - Kane, Robert Patterson, Undated
    - Kane, Robert R., 1919
    - Kane, Thomas L., 1918-1924
    - Kane, W. Thomas L., 1883-1885
    - Kazine, Ivan A., 1949
      Seeking an engineering position for him.
    - Kellogg, Paul U., 1919-1922
      Sending him $10. for The Survey.
    - Kelly, N.B., 1915-1921
      Recommendation from the Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce as a competent attorney.
    - Kerr, James, 1892 July 30
      To Herbert Walsh regarding Ute removal bill.
    - Keyser, Anna and Joseph, 1921-1922
    - King, Clyde L., 1920-1922
      To Henry Walnut; concerning program on criminal procedure.
    - Kinney, William H., 1950 March 3
      Regarding award to Mr. Fraser for prison work.
    - L, 1914-1922
    - Land Title and Trust Company, 1914-1923
    - Lane, David H., 1906
    - Lane, Francis F., 1919
    - Lane, Franklin Knight, 1917-1920
      Secretary of the Interior.
    - Laurel Hill Cemetery Company, 1914-1915
    - Lavalle, John W., 1882-1886
      From school friend.
    - Lavalle, Rosita, 1885
      Friendly letters.
    - Law, Jack, 1921
    - League to Enforce Peace, 1918
    - LeDuc, Louis, 1949
      Concerning Mrs. Stockton's estate.
    - Lehigh Coal and Navigation Company, 1915-1916
    - Leiper, E.F., 1925 November 13
      Regarding testimonial to E.K. Kane.
    - Levinson. D., 1949 November 23
      Edward A. Haley, a black man convicted of voluntary manslaughter and defended by F.F.K. in the Supreme Court, has been granted full pardon by Gov. Duff of Pennsylvania.
    - Lewis, James Hamilton, 1920
    - Lewis, John F., 1922, 1931
      Letter of introduction for cousin John A. Leiper; Concerning J.K.K. (grandfather's) portrait.
    - Lewis, Shippen, 1915-1925; 1943-1944
    - Lewis, William Draper, 1915, 1921-1922
      Concerning church and family matters.
    - Lisle, R. Mason, 1917-1918
    - Lloyd, Fannie, 1884
      Concerns raising money for "the Society".
    - Lloyd, Samuel, 1884 August 19
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1922 February 11
      Thanks Sen. Cabot for voting to extend loans to Austria.
    - Long, John Luther, 1924
    - Lord, John C., 1884-1885
    - Ludwig, Gilbert W., 1921
      Fees for work from deputy court clerk.
    - M, 1915-1926
    - McAvoy, Charles D., 1920-1921
      Regarding portrait of former president Wilson.
    - McCabe, Louis F., 1949 July 26
      Regarding unnamed trial.
    - McCartney, Harry S., 1921 September 12
      Regarding legal matters, Adamson act.
    - McCormick, M.A., 1921
    - McCormick, Vance, 1915-1919
    - McCoy, James F., 1923
    - McCracken, Robert T., 1952 February 2
      Regarding Philadelphia prison issues.
    - McCue, James, 1921 September
      Missed opportunity to visit in Dayton.
    - McDermott, William J., 1914
    - McFadden, Manus E., 1917
    - McGuckins, Teresa, 1921
    - McGuigan vs. Pennsylvania Railroad, 1906
    - Mack, Jerimiah, 1909 September 16
      Concerning legislative report.
    - McKaig, Edgar S., 1952 May 22
      Can't contribute to Home Missionary Society.
    - McMichael, Charles B., 1906 October 27
      Thanks F.F.K. and Democratic committee for nomination for Judge of Court of Common Pleas in Philadelphia.
    - MacMillan, D.B., 1919-1923
    - McPherson, John B., 1906
      Regarding Shakespeare Society and Legal Aid Society.
    - Magee, John G., 1917-1918
    - Mahany, Rowland B., 1922 January 25
      Praises F.F.K.'s efforts to promote amnesty following WWI.
    - Malatesta, Mario, 1922-1923
    - Mallery, Otto, 1948 February 13
      To Mr. St. Alban Kite of New Jersey Board of Pardons regarding visit of Starr Daily, former prisoner and prisoner advocate.
    - Mallet, Charles V., 1919-1923
    - Marquand, Allan, 1885
      Regarding reading group, Mr. Marquand's illness.
    - Marquand, Eleanor C. #1, 1921
      Concerning difficulties of Guyot Cameron.
    - Marquand, Eleanor C. #2, 1949
      Regarding health of Catherine and Helen.
    - Marr, Elizabeth M., 1949 August 15
      Bill for stenographic services; mentions House of Detention project.
    - Martin, Isadore, 1924
    - Martin, J. Willis, 1905 September 11
      Regarding recommendation for William McCleary.
    - Mayoral Campaign, 1903
      Newspaper clippings of F.F. Kane's run for mayor of Philadelphia. Sent to Thomas P. Cope, Jr.
    - Medical and Chirurgical Faculty of Maryland, 1857
      Copy of resolution regarding death of E.K.K.
    - Mereditte, Catherine K., 1905 October 3
      Regarding death of "Gertrude".
    - Meserole, Darwin, 1926, 1930, 1947
      Regarding radical politics, etc.
    - Middleton, Ellida J., 1885 February 19
      His aunt; Invites him to visit Washington DC during inauguaration.
    - Middleton, Emeline, 1885 February 19
      His cousin; thank-you note and tells story of Sam Randall, Jr. and Pres. Cleveland.
    - Middleton, Helen, 1922
    - Middleton, John, 1883-1885
      His cousin; friendly letters.
    - Miller, Frieda, 1922
    - Miller, Hobart, Undated
    - Mills, George E., 1921 November 16
      F.F.K. going to Cincinnati for law meeting.
    - Mills, Miss, 1915
    - Milton, David M., Undated
      Letters from European journey.
    - Minnich, John, 1917-1918
    - Miscellaneous, Undated
      Notes, concert program.
    - Mitchell, Langdon, 1907 March 31
      Letter of condolence on R.P.K.'s death.